Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
How did you get rich?
How did I get rich?
You know what this building is?
New York Stock Exchange?
Yes.
That's where I got rich.
What do you do?
I'm a trader on the floor of the stock exchange.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I've been doing it for 40 years.
I'm the longest standing broker in the world.
The most famous stock broker in the world.
How lucky are you to be on Wall Street?
You know who I am, don't you?
Yes, that's right.
Does he make a lot of money?
Of course.
How much money do you make?
Personally, high eight figures.
But my business right now, VaynerX, is
doing $340 million a year in revenue.
I trade between a half a billion
and a billion dollars of stock every day.
Every single day?
Every day.
You have more knowledge of money
than 99.9% of people in the world.
Give me a lesson about money that is not toxic.
We need to install it.
Everybody watching this right now.
Find a money license.
The quickest way a man loses his
money is by getting involved with a woman.
Sir, so my objective with this video that
I'm filming, I'm trying to get somebody to
let me into the New York Stock Exchange.
Is it?
You know what?
Is that possible?
This building is the New York Stock Exchange.
This is the financial capital.
This is the capital of the planet.
Trillions of dollars move through
these doors every single day.
And today, I'm doing something absolutely crazy, you guys.
I'm trying to break into the New York Stock Exchange.
And I'm not kidding.
But before we do that, since I am in New
York City right now, which is home to more millionaires
and billionaires than any city in the entire
world, I'm going to be meeting up with some
of the richest legends in all of New York City.
Guys that have actually built billion dollar
empires right out here in New York City.
So this video is about to
be insane from start to finish.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
All right, you guys, we are right now on
our way to go get our first interview out here
in New York City.
And it is none other than the legendary Gary Vee.
This guy is one of the avengers of entrepreneurship.
And I don't think you guys realize
how much money this man, Gary Vee, makes.
Well, I'll give you an idea.
It's hundreds of millions of dollars.
But we're about to go find out for the
man himself how he became wealthy and how you
watching this can become rich just
like Gary Vee in today's world.
So let's get started.
Let's go meet up with the legend himself right now.
What's going on, man?
How you doing?
It's great to see you.
Good to see you.
Who am I here with today?
Gary Vaynerchuk.
How did you make your millions?
Marketing.
Yeah.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
This guy gave me the best advice once.
Came on his show in 2018.
He told me to go all in.
And he just sold my company.
How much?
Good money.
I think my answer is good money too.
But it is hefty eight figures.
How about revenue for your business?
Vayner X, the company that I'm running day
to day right now, is going to probably do
$340 million.
$340 million in revenue this year?
In revenue.
It's a big company.
That's the funniest part about the Gary Vee
story for me when I detach myself from it.
Most people think I'm a motivational
speaker or like a content creator.
I don't think people realize how operational I am.
In fact, the joke at Vayner is as
much the COO as I am the CEO.
Not only do I like being the CEO and
set the vision and all things we're talking about,
but I'm in the traffic.
You mentioned that a lot of people,
they don't necessarily talk about your business prowess,
but you're operating a massive nine-figure company.
Gary, give me one lesson about.
You're running a business right here
that is not taught in any university.
Scaling unscalable behaviors with the human beings
that most matter to your outcome is
disproportionately the most important thing a CEO can
do and not one person talks about it.
For example, I have no time.
I'm fighting for every second, but having dinner
with nine teammates that are at year three just
to let them know I'm a human being
and want to know what they care about.
Title, money, work-life balance.
That's an hour and a half
that most people that are running company.
And by the way, that's one company I run.
VaynerSports.
The guy who runs VaynerSports.
Gary B. Brand.
VeeFriends is a very meaningful company that I'm running.
VCR Group, the restaurant group that's exploding
in New York that I'm very involved in.
I'm f***ing busy, bro.
And yet, I will fight for
non-scalable behaviors like one-on-one times, 15-minute check-ins.
It is the f***ing missing thing.
And I think as the world goes more
AI, more tech, more this, the non-scalable human interactions,
an effort you put into the people that you f***ing
roll with is about to f***ing explode in value at a
time where people continue to misunderstand its value today.
That's game right there.
I think so.
Gary, you're one of the
greatest internet marketers of our generation.
You've made brands billions of dollars.
Give me your best marketing and
branding advice for anybody in business.
Look, I'm going to do this until I f***ing
die or until the glasses come and f*** it up.
Organic social media creative is still, at
this exact second, grossly, grossly misunderstood and undervalued.
Why?
Because f***ing people can't believe.
It's almost like it's too
good to be true, I think.
I think the reason people are
f***ed up is they're like, so wait.
You post and one post can get 10
million and start the process of changing everything?
Yes, f***.
Yes, it can.
You know they don't teach that in school, right?
I know.
They teach how to do press releases
at the best comm school in the country.
It's f***ing crazy.
Getting into debt at college, if you're creative or
an entrepreneur, is the most f***ing insane thing on earth.
If your parents pay for it, go f***ing keg stand and
hook up and f***ing live the best four-year vacation of your life.
But if you're f***ing taking debt and you're an
entrepreneur or creative person, you're out of your f***ing mind.
How important is this?
The skill set of learning how to master attention.
Attention is the only currency that's going to matter.
If me and you die tomorrow,
your last message to the younger generation?
That's a really fun question.
You're going to actually die, so what
the f*** are you playing around for?
Just live your f***ing life.
Tune out everyone.
Parents, people you look up to, your contemporaries.
You've got to tune everyone the f*** out and you've got
to live your actual life for your actual one f***ing life.
Because I don't know if you know this, you were not born for a
very long time and when you f***ing die, you're going to be dead forever.
So you motherf***ers better squeeze the f***.
Out of this life.
Jesus Christ.
Stop crying and start doing.
Gary, you've got beautiful advice, my man.
I appreciate you, man.
Stay well, man.
I've got to tell you, man.
I love you, man.
You want to know something crazy?
I grew this channel to 17 million followers.
If it wasn't for you,
this channel would have never begun.
I mean that wholeheartedly.
We created one of the
biggest business channels in the world.
If it wasn't for you,
we wouldn't have become entrepreneurs, man.
Guys, we just interviewed Gary Vee.
And did you hear what he just said?
Listen, attention is everything.
It's the only thing that's going to matter.
He said organic content is still the best marketing today.
That's what I do on a daily basis.
And he's completely right, you guys.
Listen, the richest people in the world will tell you,
if you don't have people's
attention, you don't have a business.
But here's the problem.
Look, most entrepreneurs, most people
that are starting a business,
they know they need to post content.
They just don't have the time.
And that is exactly where Opus Clip comes in.
Opus Clip is the most powerful tool
that I've seen to help people create content.
And Opus has evolved way beyond just clipping.
It is now the most powerful AI
growth tool for creators and business owners.
It automatically pulls in your YouTube videos
or videos from your Google Drive or Dropbox.
Anywhere you keep your footage.
And it literally finds the best moments for you.
It adds captions, creates hooks, b-roll,
and even schedules your post for you.
I mean, this is literally insane.
It's like having an entire
editing team all in one tool.
I use it to turn long interviews,
all the interviews you see me do,
into short viral clips that I
post on Instagram, TikTok, and YouTube Shorts.
And it's all done within minutes.
So if you run a business
and you're trying to get more attention,
and you know that you need it,
trust me, you know you need it.
You don't need a studio or a bunch of editors.
You just need Opus Clip.
So to get started, go down and click
the link in the description of this video.
And you're going to get
Opus for free for one week
and 50% off your first three months using Opus.
So I want you to watch
how these ideas turn into attention
and your business and life changes forever.
With that being said, let's go get our next interview.
All right, you guys, as you can
see, we made it to Wall Street.
I'm right outside of the New York Stock Exchange.
Like I said earlier, guys, this
is the financial capital of the world.
Some of the richest people in
New York come down to these streets
and move money in this building right there.
So today, I'm going to try and do something crazy.
I'm going to try to get into
the New York Stock Exchange for you guys.
So let's see what the inside looks like
and what some of the richest people do
out here to make the money work for them.
So let's go see who we can find.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, how did you get rich?
Oh, sorry.
Real quick, sir.
Do you work on the Stock Exchange?
Excuse me, sir.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
A millionaire?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Do you work on Wall Street?
No.
Excuse me, guys.
Question for you all.
Do you guys work on Wall Street?
No.
I know you, Chad.
You know me?
Yeah.
Listen, I'm not a millionaire, man.
I can't help it.
No, I got you, brother.
I'm trying to get into the Stock Exchange, actually.
They got events going on.
Yeah.
So I got to find a wealthy
stockbroker out here to let me in then.
The closing bell is at 4 o'clock.
Okay.
So you probably see him
flowing out between 4 to 4.30.
Perfect.
That might be a time to catch someone.
Yeah.
Thank you, sir.
I appreciate that, man.
Let me take a picture.
Excuse me, sir.
Real quick.
Come here for one minute.
I see you.
We're not that level.
No, no.
Hey.
Real quick.
Real quick, though.
Hey.
Can you get me into the Stock Exchange?
You want me to get in there?
Oh, man.
All right, you guys.
You see, it is nearly impossible to get these
people to stop and talk and do an interview,
let alone think about how hard it is to
try and get into the Stock Exchange, you guys.
But look, these people aren't stopping.
They're going from meeting to meeting.
They don't want to do the
interview, but I'm not stopping either.
Okay.
I'm not going to stop until I get one
of these wealthy individuals to stop, give me the game,
and get me in that damn Stock Exchange.
So stay tuned.
Let's go see who we can find.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
I have a question for you.
Yeah.
How did you get rich?
How did I get what?
Rich?
Yeah.
You look like money, brother.
You look good.
I look like money?
Yes, sir.
Thanks a lot.
I appreciate it.
What line of business are you in?
What?
I'm a stockbroker.
You're a stockbroker?
Yeah.
Give me the best financial
advice to help the younger generation.
Let's say I don't have a good mentor.
Give me one money lesson you would
instill in me and the younger generation.
One money lesson?
One money lesson.
Stay away from women.
Wait, wait.
Real quick.
Was that one of your advices?
Yeah.
Stay away from women.
The quickest way a man loses his
money is by getting involved with a woman.
You asked me for it.
I told you.
Let's be honest, dude.
So did you fall victim to that?
No, I did not fall victim to that,
but I see a lot of guys doing that.
How did you stay disciplined then?
I see the discipline.
United States Marine Corps.
You were in the Marine Corps.
Absolutely.
And is it safe to say there's
a correlation between physical fitness and financial success?
It's a discipline.
Discipline.
There's a certain discipline to it.
I follow stoicism.
You got to be very stoic.
Yeah.
All right?
Everything is fleeting.
So if you do everything the right way.
The first way you want to live life right.
First of all, look at yourself in the mirror.
Okay?
Judge yourself first.
All right?
You only answer to yourself and God.
Okay?
Everything else is fleeting.
Fame is fleeting.
Fortune is fleeting.
This video is fleeting.
People will see it, but they'll forget about tomorrow.
So just be true to yourself
and always do the right thing.
And then this is what will come.
Was authenticity one of your secrets to success?
No.
My mother taught me everything.
My secrets to success.
And she also taught me, stay away from women.
I'm giving you all the secrets.
Yeah.
This is incredible.
I love this.
Go ahead.
Take me back to the
most life-changing conversation you ever had.
What is the best advice you ever got?
And then I'm also late.
I got to go.
So this is going to be your last conversation.
My uncle told me when I was a little
boy, your friends are going to come and go, but
your enemies will accumulate.
And I kept that advice.
Did you choose your enemies wisely?
I don't have any enemies because they, exactly.
What, what?
I really, really got it.
A financial nugget to help the younger generation.
You're a stockbroker.
You're moving money left and right.
It's best in your bank.
Wait, wait.
But are banks out to, they're
about to make money for themselves.
You can get a guarantee from your bank.
You can get a CD.
You can get all kinds of guarantees from your bank.
You can't get that from a-
What's the best investment you
can make in today's world though?
Because the banks, there's only
like a percentage of interest.
Okay.
There's other avenues.
You're really pushing your luck down with me.
Okay.
I told you one more.
Yeah.
All right.
So that was it.
I got you, brother.
Have a good one, brother, man.
Have a good one.
Hey, as you guys can see, man, I think
if I asked one more question, he probably would
have popped me, but you know, I
had to stretch out for that game.
And I got to say, man, I liked that interview.
It was on the go.
It was scrappy, but we
got some nuggets out of him.
Great interview out here on Wall Street.
We got to keep this one rolling, you guys.
Come on.
All right, you guys.
So look what just came out
of the New York Stock Exchange.
I mean, this looks like a pile of
money that just came out here, you guys.
We're going to have to walk up and
see how these people got rich, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
This guy.
Yes, sir.
I've just been getting your Instagram feeds.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Oh, boy.
Four years ago.
And what line of business?
Technology.
What do you do in tech?
CRO for Snowflake.
Did you guys just go public?
We went public five years ago.
During COVID, couldn't ring the
bell, so this is our moment.
Do you recommend entrepreneurs take their company public?
Because there's a risk there as well when you
bring in all that capital, you bring in voting shares.
What do you think about going
public as opposed to staying private?
Good question.
I think there's a lot of value in
staying private until you have a well-defined market.
You've got a well-defined go-to-market plan.
And then when you need the funding, you go execute.
So you're a chief revenue officer.
I am.
What's the most...
I have to snag him.
I'm so sorry.
We got $17 million.
This is the best marketing he could do.
I know.
This is literally the best marketing he could do.
All right, just keep it rolling.
Hey, we're keeping this rolling, man.
I'm sorry.
Not...
I didn't ask.
Oh!
Real quick.
Can I finish real quick with
you real quick for one minute?
We'll do 30 seconds.
30 seconds is cool.
All right.
So you're the chief revenue officer.
What do you think most people get wrong
about cash flow when they're building a company?
Because you hear all the time
that cash flow is what saves business.
Pre-profitability, cash flow is king.
What does that mean?
You've got to have equal cash flow.
You've got to be positive, operating margin positive.
Cash flow is everything until profitability comes.
Then you get S&P 500, and you get a whole
different kind of return on investment from a shareholder perspective.
Have you always been in the tech industry?
Always, my entire career.
Why?
I love it.
It's changing the world.
Do you think if business owners aren't
leveraging AI, they're going to be left behind?
Absolutely.
Why?
It's like the internet.
If you're not on the internet, wave your dead.
It's going to replace Uber drivers.
It potentially could.
Self-driving business.
So next five to 10 years, what do you
see the future of tech kind of transforming into?
Five years is tough to predict, my friend.
In this world, it's moving at a torrid pace.
12 to 18 months, that's all you got.
Yeah, okay.
Give me the next 12 months.
What's the number one thing people need
to be adopting in their business right now?
They're going to be using AI to basically
augment human behavior, accelerate processes, eliminate risk, accelerate revenue.
It's all about moving fast.
As somebody who's an executive at a billion-dollar company.
You're awesome, by the way.
I watch you all the time.
Congratulations on all your success.
You're an executive at a billion-dollar company.
The best financial advice you
can give to the younger generation.
Give me something tactical, not taught in school.
You're at a publicly traded company.
Right.
Give me something tactical, not
taught in school about money.
Give me the best money advice
you can give to the younger generation.
Best money advice I can give?
Save.
Save everything you possibly can.
You can't save your way to wealth, though.
You can save your way to
being financially secure in the future.
You've got to build up wealth.
Don't worry about W-2s.
W-2 is not necessary.
Maybe it'll help you pay the rent.
It's not going to pay for your college tuition.
Where do the richest people put their money?
No, no.
In Snowflake Stock.
All right, you guys.
So, my guy, safe to say,
he has a team full of gatekeepers.
They wouldn't let me get the contact.
They wouldn't even let me get the interview.
But I had to get as much
out of him as I possibly could.
And he just gave a hell of an interview
for what it was worth for the time being.
So, shout out to that man right there.
But we've got to get this
next one out here, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
How did you get rich?
How did I get rich?
You know what this building is?
New York Stock Exchange?
Yes.
That's where I got rich.
What do you do?
I'm a trader on the floor of the Stock Exchange.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I've been doing it for 40 years.
I'm the longest standing broker in the world.
The most famous stock broker in the world.
How long have you been on Wall Street?
You know who I am, don't you?
Yes, that's right.
Does he make a lot of money?
Of course.
How much money do you make?
I trade between a half a billion
and a billion dollars of stock every day.
You trade that every single day?
Every day.
I go all over the world and bring
the richest people to help the younger generation.
Can I get a minute with
you for my chat over there?
A hundred percent.
You're literally the Wolf of Wall Street.
You know what?
I don't like that connotation, but yes, I am.
And probably there were years where I
perhaps was the Wolf of Wall Street.
What is the best financial advice
you could give to the younger generation?
You have more knowledge of money
than 99.9% of people in the world.
Give me a lesson about money that is not toxic
or that you would install in everybody watching this right now.
So one of the things I always talk
about, and I have a nice social media platform,
and I love talking to younger people,
even as young as 13, 14, 15,
because they're the greatest
consumer generation in the world.
And one of the most important things
is to invest in stocks and not stuff.
We love to buy stuff, right?
Everybody, if I were to say
to you, look in your closet.
We've got tons of stuff.
We go on Instagram and we buy
things and then we have it delivered yesterday
and we'll pay more than
it's the value of the thing.
And everything we buy goes down in value.
Pretty much most things we buy when we
need something, when we have an urge, right?
And we have to have it, goes
down in value the minute you buy it.
So the whole idea is to change your whole mindset
and invest in things that perhaps
are going to go up in value.
So we love to buy things and stuff.
And so that whole mindset to invest in stocks,
and not stuff is one of the,
that was something I wish I had known.
There's so much value in that.
It's amazing.
I've heard a number of the guys you interview, billionaires,
who said that, you know, have multiple streams of revenue
and let your money work for you.
And that's one of the ways it can happen.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yes, I've been virtually penniless.
My parents had money.
So there was no point in my life where
I did not have a little bit of a backstop.
But there was a period of time, 2006,
7 and 8, when I hit rock bottom.
I was not making any money.
And for a couple of weeks, I cowered.
I was under the covers.
But I had a wife and children.
And I knew no opportunity was going
to find me hiding under the covers,
just sort of unable to really move forward.
So I decided, you know what?
I'm going to get up every day and
dress up, show up, and go to work,
not tell anybody what was going on,
and act as if I was making money.
I did that for two years.
I didn't make a dime for two years.
And I kind of bobbed and weaved.
I was able to sort of support my
family on borrowing money and credit cards and whatnot.
And then one day on the subway, I ran into a
guy I had done business with years ago on Wall Street.
And he was, he...
I always get choked up.
And he asked me how I was doing.
And it was the first time
I actually said, you know what?
I'm broke.
He goes, what do you do?
You're going...
I said, I'm going to work every day because
no opportunity is going to find me at home.
And he goes, you know what?
We traded together for years.
Why don't we start to trade again?
And next day, I started...
I built a trading strategy around what's in here.
We started to trade.
We grew.
And we ended up having a
wonderful relationship for another 20 years.
I realized that an opportunity is not going
to find you hiding in the back room.
You have to be open to the signal.
So it's safe to say you can't become a...
You can't become a millionaire working from home.
No, you can't.
We've seen everybody go through
what they went through with COVID.
And a lot of people still
are not going back to work.
Productivity is really important.
Waking up, showing up, suiting up.
Know that in any given day, if
you look for opportunity, you'll find it.
What's your name?
Peter Tuchman.
Peter, if me and you died tomorrow,
and you had one more guy in
principle to leave with the younger generation,
what would that be?
Now, I'll tell you something.
I've been doing this for 40 years.
I've been through so much.
Being broke for three years.
Losing my brother, my parents.
My wife died of cancer last year.
Gone.
Gone through so much.
I almost died of COVID.
I was given three months to live.
What was that one thing that kept you going?
Because you've been through so
much adversity in the last year.
That I love what I do.
I don't need to post a bunch of pictures of
me on the back of a Bugatti with stacks of 10,000.
But if I can share what I found,
I don't want to be
on the mountaintop all by myself.
Find something you love to do.
Get really good at it.
And embrace the younger generation.
You got amazing advice, sir.
You're wonderful.
Thank you so much for your time.
Can I get your contact?
Absolutely.
Sir, so my objective with this video that I'm filming,
I'm trying to get somebody to
let me into the New York soccer.
Exchange.
Is it?
Yeah, let's do it.
You know what?
Is that possible?
Can we go in for a minute real quick?
Yes, we can.
For you, I'll do it.
It's special.
Just for you.
Come on.
Let's go.
I appreciate that.
Go.
Go, go, go.
You go first.
And we're just doing this show.
So this is the main room of the soccer exchange.
And this is where you trade the half
a billion dollars to a billion dollars a day.
Exactly.
What is that even like?
How are you getting that
much volume and that much money?
In order for somebody to trust you enough to
give you that much stock, it's a big deal.
It's taken years and years like that.
So there's different order flow that comes down to us.
We have customers.
And then we're also trading the S&P 500.
And so, you know, you'd be amazed that,
you know, we trade 1.2 billion shares of stock.
Dollar notional value of a stock, right?
So 1,000 shares of Visa,
that's a $400 or $500 stock.
That's a lot of money.
That's hundreds of thousands of dollars.
So even though it seems
like a billion dollars, it's actually.
Not that much.
They probably trade almost a trillion dollars of value here
on the floor with the 3,000 plus publicly listed companies.
Come into the world here.
So in this room, at one point, we had
five rooms like this where we traded stock before technology.
But now with all of this, I can send
out, you know, 1,000 orders in five, ten seconds.
It used to take a long
time as an individual on paper.
Is the bell in here as well?
The bell is over there.
Come walk around.
It's amazing to be here
and when it's quiet like that.
That's the best.
The bell.
So if you think about it, since 1903, the opening bell and the closing bell is a very exclusive ceremony where heads of
state, presidents, prime ministers, CEOs of listed companies, CEOs of IPOs, initial public offerings, celebrities and charities ring the opening or closing bell.
What's your last message to the younger generation?
You know what?
Surround yourself by people who have what you want.
It's really important.
And understand that money, it does not buy you happiness.
Money buys you freedom.
That's all it's about.
It doesn't buy you happiness in any way.
Money does a funny thing to people.
It sets you in a state, whether you
have a lot of it or none of it.
It can really curate your life.
And so just be aware of
its value and the dangers of it.
You got amazing advice, sir.
Thank you so much.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video.
We've finally gotten to the New York Stock Exchange.
I need you guys to stop what you're doing right now and like and
subscribe for amazing content every week, guys, because nobody's created this kind of content.
Every week, I'm bringing you guys the craziest business owners
in the entire world, the billionaires, the multi-billionaires, you name it.
But do yourself a huge favor.
Go down to the link in the description of this video to join
the number one community, the most powerful entrepreneur network in the entire world.
Guys, every week, I give you direct access to the
millionaires and billionaires that I interview here on this channel.
So I can't wait to see you on the inside.
But that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.